Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS 180 MSS 180
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: American Genius (2006)
  - Series XI, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 420-425 with three iterations, Undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 430-434, with E-Mail from Lynne Tillman to Steve, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, several annotated copies pages 1, 424, notes and fragments, Undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Steve's" (1 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Steve's" (2 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Steve's" (3 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - American Genius Draft "End Desktop", Undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - American Genius Draft Pages 2-91, 32-33, Undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - American Genius "From December 17th Draft", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - American Genius Full Draft pages 1-123 (1 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - American Genius Full Draft pages 124-284 (2 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - American Genius Full Draft pages 285-423 (3 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - American Genius "Last Pages as of 9/11/04, 11 Sept. 2004 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - American Genius "Last Pages", 19 Sept. 2004 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - American Genius Notes and Annotated Draft (1 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - American Genius Notes and Annotated Draft (2 of 3), Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - American Genius Notes and Annotated Draft (3 of 3), Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - American Genius Research File, Skin, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - American Genius SIngle Spaced Draft pages 41-120, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - American Skin #28 Annotated Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - American Skin #28 Annotated Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - American Skin #29 Annotated Draft 9 Dec. 2003 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - American Skin #29 Annotated Draft 9 Dec. 2003 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - American Skin #33 Annotated Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - American Skin #33 Annotated Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - American Skin Annotated Draft dated Dec. 14, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - American Skin "Done in Germany" pages 349-409, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - American Skin "Skin 27" (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      Part 2 is in: Box 21, Folder 1 Part 3 is in: Box 22, Folder 27
    - "Costume Ball" Sketches and Noted toward American Genius and the Undiagnosed, Undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Instead, May 29, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Instead, Undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Instead, Undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Instead, Undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Instead, Undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Instead, Undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Instead - Annotated, June 18, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Instead - Annotated, Undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Instead of Nothing - Annotated Draft, Undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Instead "Read This 2/13/01 Art in General", Feb. 13, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Kingsley Hall Draft, Undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Seance Revisions, Nov. 2004 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Skin 18 (3 of 3), Undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
      Part 1 is in: Box 22, Folder 13 Part 2 is in: Box 21, Folder 1
    - Skin Annotated Draft (1 of 2), 14 Aug. 2002 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Skin Annotated Draft (2 of 2), 14 Aug. 2002 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Skin coverpage "edited, gone through, and input"; Folder "looms, edited, not imput", Undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Series XII: Essay and Story Collections
  Series XII: Essay and Story Collections contains materials pertaining to Lynne Tillman's several short story works. These materials consist of research, annotated drafts, reviews, etc. This series is divided into four subseries:
  A: Absence Makes the Heart
  B: Madame Realism Complex
  C: The Broad Picture
  D: This Is Not It
  - Series XII, Subseries A: Absence Makes the Heart (1991)
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Annotated Draft, Undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Annotated Draft, Undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Collected Short Pieces - Including "Myself as a Menu", "Dead Talk" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Collected Short Pieces (2 of 2), Undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Component Pieces, Annotated Draft, Undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Copy and Annotated Draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Absence Makes the Heart first draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Promotion and Publicity, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Publicity and Reviews, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Reviews and Publicity, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - AKA Megatroid, Undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - AKA Megatroid annotated, cut and paste, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Dead Talk annotated draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Diary of a Masochist annotated draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Diary of a Masochist annotated draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - "Hung Up", Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - "Hung Up", Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Imitation of Life, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Marilyn Monroe: Dead Talk - 1st version annotated, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Marilyn Monroe / Dead Talk and Fixing Memory annotated papers, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Original Draft handwritted - Weird Fucks, Undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - "Other Movies", Undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - "Other Movies" annotated, Undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - "The Day Before We Moved In...", Undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - The Trouble with Beauty - 1st version, Undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - The Trouble with Beauty - for Conjunctions, Undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - The Trouble with Beauty - Patrick's Copyediting, Undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - The Trouble with Beauty - Two copies of annotated draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Wierd Fucks, Undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Weird Fucks, Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Weird Fucks - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Weird Fucks draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Weird Fucks draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Weird Fucks "It was Ramadan..." pages 1-10, Undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Weird Fucks - Original Manuscript with annotations, Undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Words Without Pictures, Undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Series XII, Subseries B: Madame Realism Complex (1992)
    - Dynasty Reruns, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Dynasty Reruns: "Treasure Houses of Great Britain" - Art in America, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Ellis "Madame Realism", Undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Madame Realism, Undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - The Madame Realism Complex, Undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - The Madame Realism Complex, Undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - The Madame Realism Complex (1 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - The Madame Realism Complex (2 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - The Madame Realism Complex / How I Became One of the Invisible by David Rattray, Undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - The Madame Realism Complex press and publicity, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - The Madame Realism Complex publicity, Undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - The Madame Realism Complex - Trade Blurb, Undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Madame Realism Takes a Look, Undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - "Madame Realism's Imitation of Life", Undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Myself as a Menu - excerpts from Something in Progress, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - On the Road with Madame Realism, Undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Reviews of "Madame Realism Complex"; Native Agents Title, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Series XII, Subseries C: The Broad Picture
    - The Broad Picture - Advance, uncorrected proof, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - The Broad Picture - Beeksbee Books Promotions, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - The Broad Picture - Cover, Undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - The Broad Picture: Essays - Press and Publicity, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - The Broad Picture: Essays 1987-1996 - Table of contents and Preface, Undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - The Broad Picture Manuscript, Phil's Comments, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - The Broad Picture publicity, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - The Broad Picture - Tillman essay collection, 1985-1992 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Essays with selecte/possible table of contents (1 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Essays with selected/possible table of contents (2 of 2), 1980-1994 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Like Rockets and Television II, Undated (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Looking for Trouble - Frieze, Undated (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Love Song for Ray Charles, Undated (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Telling Tales - early draft, Undated (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Series XII, Subseries D: This Is Not It (2002)
    - American Institute of Graphic Arts - Excellence in Design for "This is Not It", 2003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - CameraWork Benefit Auction, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence for "This is Not It", 2002 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Juan Munoz for Parkett - Oversize folders, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - "Lust for Loss", Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - The Official "This is Not It" Awards with self portrait (polaroid), Undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Pleasure isn't a Pretty Picture" Reading, Undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - This is Not It - Permissions, Lists, Drafts, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - This is Not It - Galleys (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - This is Not It - Galleys (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - This is Not It - Publicity, Reviews, ad Material, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - TV Tales annotated draft, Undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Series XIII: Other Works and Activities
  Series XIII: Other Works and Activities contains materials related to Lynne Tillman's works other than her published books/films. These works include short stories published in magazines and anthologies, readings at event, art exhibitions, editing, and teaching. This series also contains the publicity for these works. This series is divided into five subseries:
  A: Writing, Readings, and Artwork
  B: Editing
  C: Publicity
  D: Notes and Fragments
  E: Teaching
  - Series XIII, Subseries A: Writing, Readings, and Artwork
    - 3 Short Pieces - Bad News, A Dead Summer, Boots & Remorse (1 of 3), Undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - 3 Short Pieces (2 of 3), Undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - 3 Short Pieces (3 of 3), Undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - "21 TV Tales" for Barbara Kruger, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - 90's Fiction Conference - University of Sussex, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - 1977: From the Archive - Franklin Furnace Archive exhibition curated by Lynne Tillman (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - A: A Novel - New School Panel, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - "Absence Makes Art" and earlier "Never Leave" - Jim Hodges, Undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Aiden Shaw for Nest, Undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Allen Ginsberg Paragraph by Lynne Tillman on his death, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Alt. Yours, Undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Amanda Foreman profile by Lynne Tillman in Elle Magazine, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Andy Warhol Conference, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Aperture Magazine - Lynne Tillman interviewsGary Schneider, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Articles regarding Charles Henri Ford, Undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - The Assault on Fiction / The Truth About Fiction, Undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - The Assault of Fiction / The Truth About Fiction, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - "Bad News" - Elizabeth Stories, Undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Bad News Typescript, Undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Barbara Bloom - Research and Notes, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Barbara Kruger Images for TV Tales, Undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Barbara Kruger Interview and Transcript, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      Separated Materials
      Deaccessioned and returned to donor, 2012.
    - BBC - Lynne Tillman Contribution "Night", 2003 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Beat the Devil "Knockin on Heaven's Door" Treatment, Undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - "Beats on the Beach" annotated draft for Voice Literary Supplement, Undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Beauty and the Beast Treatment, Undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Between C & D - New Writing from the Lower East Side Fiction Magazine - "Dead Talk", 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Between C & D Benefit - Reading by Lynne Tillman, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Blind Spot - excerpt from "To Find Words", 2002 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Bob Flanagan: In Memoriam to a Former Poster Boy, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Bob Flanagan Memorial Reading, October 1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Bomb Manuscripts - Lynne Tillman interviews Petah Coyne (1 of 2), Undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Bomb Manuscript - Lynne Tillman interviews Petah Coyne (2 of 2), Undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - "Boots" drafts, Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Brighton Writer's Conference (materials and paper presented), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Buhl essay for Linda Yablonsky with transcript of Lynne Tillman interview, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - "But There's a Family Resemblance" drafts - Connected to Shoot the Family exhibition, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Cagney and Lacey piece - "Looking for Trouble (rupture)!", Undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - "Call and No Responce" - Folder: "Al Green", Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - "Call it Local / Specter of the Rose", Undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Call it Local / Specter of the Rose - annotated draft and final proof, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Carla Car Story - "The Way We Are" a Simple Idea, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Charles Henri Ford Franklin Furnace Flue - Interview: Lynne Tillman and Clive Philpot, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Chelsea Hotel: A Magazine for the Arts - Lynne Tillman piece translated into German by Peter Torberg, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Chenetier Journal - Selection of Lynne Tillman's work (French and English), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Cinderella, Undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - "Come and Go" manuscript (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - "Come and Go" manuscript (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Commercial Writing - NY Post, American Federation of the Arts, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - "Complicity" - Day of Hope, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Conference: Beyond the Boundary: Men, Race, and Culture, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Conference: Finding Fanon: Critical Geneologies, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Conjunctions - Lynne Tillman essay "Edith Wharton: A Mole in the House of Modern", 1997 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Contact Zone Symposium at Drawing Center - Organized by Renee Green, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Core Sample - Email Correspondence, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Core Sample - Portland, Oregon: Packet of materials, removed from plastic wrapper, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Core Sample - Tillman critique, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - "Criminal Love" for German Vogue (Also called Relentless Love), 1995 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Cultural Criticism articles/reviews - Elle, NY Times Book Review, Undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Daily Life / Living with Contradictions - annotated draft, Undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Day of Hope, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - "A Dead Summer" - still life excersizes for Art Paper, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Deb Margolin research and interview transcripts - Village Voice Political Art 3/1990, 1985-1990 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Devotion: Writers' Retrospectives - Lynne Tillman included, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - "Diary of a Masochist" Manuscript - published in PAN #2, Undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Diary of a NY Writer on Tour in England, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - "Do No Harm" - Contribution to Art Start Silent Auction, Undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - "Don't Cry...Work" Conversations with Meret Oppenheim and Carla Liss and Lynne Tillman for Art and Artists Magazine, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - "Don't Cry...Work" Art and Artists 8:7, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Don't Look Now - organized by Joshua Decter - Group show includes Lynne Tillman, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Don't Shave Your Legs Manifesto, Undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Drastic Measures - Screenplay collaboration of Lynne Tillman and Jane Weinstock, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Drastic Measures screenplay, Undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Drastic Measures screenplay, 10 March, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Drawing Center, Nightlight readings - Fay Weldon, Lynne Tillman, Thomas Beller, Undated (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - "Dynasty Reruns", Undated (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Early Poetry, Undated (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Elle article - "Parallel Lives", Undated (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Excerpt from "Not Dreams NYC", Undated (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Evidence: Photography and Site at Wexner Center for the Arts - Lynne Tillman wrote an essay for the exhibition (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - False! The New Counterfeiters - Madame Realism's Imitation of Life annotated draft, Undated (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Fence - Periodically Speaking at New York Public Library, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - "Flatterers Must Be Shunned" - Lynne Tillman and Stuart Home, Put About: A Critical Anthology on Independent Publishing, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Food for Thought Slides, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Ford, Charles Henri - The Poet in Kathmandu manuscript (1 of 2), Undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Ford, Charles Henri - The Poet in Kathmandu manuscript (2 of 2), Undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Franklin Furnace exhibit of Rare Bookworks - curated by Lynne Tillman, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Fred Hughes Loft - Object Love / Mr. Somebody, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Frieze articles - Being John Malkovick, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Future Dictionary - McSweeney's, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - "Futurist Cookbook" - Voice Literary Supplement, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - The Garment Bag - faxed from John Cale to Lynne Tillman and five black and white contact sheets, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Gary Schneider interview for Aperture, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Gerard Malanga, Lisa Baumbardner, Lynne Tillman interview, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - German Vogue - O.J. Simpson article, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - German Vogue - Questions, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - "Give Us Some Dirt" annotated drafts, Undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - "Give Us Some Dirt" research, Undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Godfather piece for Sight and Sound magazine, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Greg Bordowith catalog - "My Post Modernism", "From Skin", 2002 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - "Gurgles, Sucks, Echoes" - Promotion for Lynne Tillman's text, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Haleyon Reading with Matt Sharpe, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Harry Matthews Interview, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Headshots - Auta Rosenberg Photos and essay by Lynne Tillman - Previews and Publicity, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - "Here We Go" manuscript for Go (1 of 4), Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - "Here We Go" manuscript (2 of 4), Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - "Here We Go" manuscript (3 of 4), Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - "Here We Go" manuscript (4 of 4), Undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - "Historical Noise" Liner notes for John Zorn's CD Krista Knacht - also Richard Foreman's piece, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - "Hole Story" - Voice Literary Supplement, Undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - "I Shot Andy Warhol" for Frieze, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - An Impossible Man - copyedited manuscript, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - The Interpretation of Facts, Undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Jeff Koons Panel at Guggenheim Athens - Madame Realism essay and schedule, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - John Cale interview / Paris; Christian Belaygue, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Judith Grossman interviews Lynne Tillman, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Julia Scher interviewed by Lynne Tillman - Lukasstern, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - "Jump to It" and NY Times article "Vacation Checklist", 1994 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Kathy Acker Panel - Lynne Tillman is moderator of Round Table, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - "Kids" and "Alt. Yrs", Undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - "Kids" review for Abby Nolan of the Village Voice, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Labor Days Anthology including Lynne Tillman - advance proof, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - The Last Words are Andy Warhol - Review "A: A Novel", Undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - "Later" Black Clock, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Laura Letinsky exhibit catalogue - Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Leonardo Magazine - "Madame Realism's 1999", 1992 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Les Harris interview for Nest - interview transcript (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Les Harris essay for Nest - drafts and research (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Letters - Felice Bauer, Undated (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Library of Congress regarding "Two Serious Ladies" copyright, 1980-1986 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - The Literary Insomniac Anthology "Reckless Disregard", 1994 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - The Literary Review: An International Journal of Contemporary Writing - includes Lynne Tillman's "Shadow of Doubt", 2006 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - "Little Tales of New York" for Nicholas Royle - New Observations, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - "Looking for Trouble" - Frieze, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - A Lost City of Words - For Kiki - photos and narrative, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - "Lost Pictures" and reworking of "Words without Pictures", 1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Love Sentence, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Love Sentence - adapted from Lynne Tillman story by Katherine Deickman, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Love Sentence - Drafts and source material (1 of 2), Undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Love Sentence - Drafts and source material (2 of 2), Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Love Sentence - Manuscripts, Undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Love Sentence - Source material - opera, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - "Love Science" published in American Imago, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - "Low Tableau: Writers on Privacy" at PS1 transcript, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - "Lust for Loss" - Madame Realism June 1994 Voice Literary Supplement (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Lynne Tillman's "Anomie in the U.K.: The Little Book Tour that Could" in The Village Voice, 14 Aug. 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Lynne Tillman articles in German, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Lynne Tillman blurb for Nan Goldin, Undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Lynne Tillman Book Reviews, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Lynne Tillman - Broadway Spectacolor, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Lynne Tillman and Clive Phillpot interview Charles Henri Ford, Undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Lynne Tillman "Cops" unpublished - contribution to Matthew Bourgois, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Lynne Tillman essay for exhibition catalogue - Roni Horn, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Lynne Tillman events, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Lynne Tillman events, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 24)